# Resha Puspita Dewi

Portfolio | LinkedIn | GitHub | Tech Stacks

Location: Jakarta Metropolitan Area, Indonesia Email: reshapuspitadewi@gmail.com | Mobile: +6282130320607

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

I am a detail-oriented and motivated individual, driven by a genuine curiosity and passion for software development. I have gained proficiency in **React.js and Tailwind CSS**, as well as familiarity with **Node.js, MongoDB, and Next.js**. My experiences has sharpened my critical thinking skill and taught me to keep the user in mind while developing products.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages : JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Java, Kotlin, Ruby, .NET

**Frameworks** : Vue.js, React.js, Next.js, Express, Node.js, Tailwind CSS

Libraries : Framer Motion, Redux Toolkit, React Router, React Query, Pinia

**Databases** : MongoDB, SQL Server

**Dev Tools** : Visual Studio, VS Code, Git, Postman, REST Client

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Software Developer**

Jul 2023 - Present

Central Bank of Indonesia

WFO – Jakarta Metropolitan Area, Indonesia

- Participated in backend development using .NET Core and frontend development using Postman, Figma, Vue.js 3
  and Tailwind CSS
- · Actively fixing bug that associated with issues on JIRA
- · Collaborated with cross-functional teams to achieve the project matched the defined timeline

## Front End Developer Sagara Technology

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

WFO – Bandung, West Java, Indonesia

- Acquired proficiency in utilizing technologies such as AntDesign and Next.js
- Participated in project execution, including bug fixing using Postman, UI slicing using Figma, and implementing features in both internal and client project using React.js and Tailwind CSS
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams, resulting in improved product quality and user experience

#### **UX Designer Intern**

Feb 2022 – May 2022

Prosa.ai

Remote – Bandung, West Java, Indonesia

- Learned about design thinking and best practices in UX design, applying new knowledge to design projects using tool such as **Figma and UsabilityHub**
- · Conducted a usability study for a newly launched product, recruiting 10 participants within two-weeks time-frame
- · Worked closely with the product manager to discuss design and interaction requirements

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Institut Teknologi Bandung**

Bachelor of Science in Information System and Technology

August 2017 - March 2023

## TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS

# Web Development Bootcamp Graduate (2020)

Certificate

- Impact Byte's Web Development Bootcamp is designed to give students a comprehensive understanding of web development, from the front end to the back end. Over the course of the bootcamp, I built final projects using technologies such as React, Node.js, and Express, as well as database management with MongoDB.
- Acquired skills: React.js, Node.js, Express, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git, Bootstrap, Styled-Components, Bulma, Material UI